Finding Aid for the Zoia Horn Papers LSC.2262
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research and Writings, 1960-2014
  - Right to Know, 1986-2001 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Right to Know: Data Center Project, 1982-1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Right to Know: Data Center Reviews, 1982-1991 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Right Wing Groups, 1978-2004 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Robbins (Louise), 1994-2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Roberts (Lillian), 1970-2011 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Rom (Pat), 1988-2002 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Russia and Ukraine, 1979-2011 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Samoto - San Francisco, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Public Library: Fees, 1995-1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco Public Library: Press, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Schiller (Herb), 1992-2004 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Secrecy, 1982-2006 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Seldes (George), 1970-1996 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - September 11, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
  - September 11: Civil Liberties, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - September 11: Comments and Dissent, 2001-2007 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - September 11: Department of Homeland Security, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - September 11: Peace Actions, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - September 11: War, 1998-2002 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Service (John), 1999-2010 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Sexism - Slavery, 1996-2008 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Social Security, 2001-2013 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - South Africa, 1988-1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - South Africa: Apartheid Movements, 1987-1990 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Soviet-American Peace Walk, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Stanislaus Public Library, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Strharsky Family, 1992-2008 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Suicide, 2000-2013 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Supreme Court, 2002-2013 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Scrip Program, 2011-2013 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 2011-2013 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications Act, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Templeton (Rini), 1984-2006 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Terrorism, 1998-2007 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Terrorism Information and Prevention System, 2002-2005 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Theatre, 2000-2007 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Toronto, 2005-2008 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Torture, 2004-2009 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Toy (Ernie), 1999-2012 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - United States Congress, 2001-2005 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - United States Foreign Relations, 1991-2003 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - United States Health Care - United States Military, 1991-2007 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - University of California Berkeley - Universal Deal, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Violence, 2001-2012 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Voting, 2002-2013 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Walker - Wallace, 2008-2013 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - War, 1970-2003 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - War: Antiwar Demonstrations, 2001-2013 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - War: Tax Resistance, 1969-1971 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Warren Township, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Washington DC, 1987-2002 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Washington DC: Trip, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Wealth, 1992-2012 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Wershba (Joe), 1966-2011 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Whistleblowers, 1980-2013 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Wolfston (Betsy), 2002-2012 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Women, 1991-2013 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Women's Health Initiative, 2000-2006 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Writings: Citizens Letters, 1973-2005 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Writings: Future Research, 1919-2013 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Writings: Horn (Zoia), 1964-2014 (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Writings: Reviews, 1975-2002 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Writings: Unfinished, 1973-1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Zoia!, 1995-2014 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Zoia!: Manuscript, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 2-3)
  - Zoia!: MacFarland Publishers, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Zoia!: Translation, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Zoia!: Reviews, 1995-2002 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Journals: Alaska, 2000 (Box 35)
  - Journals:China, 1978 (Box 35)
  - Journals: England, 1969-1979 (Box 35)
  - Journals: Europe, 1962-1971 (Box 35)
  - Journals: France, 1997 (Box 36)
  - Journals: Greece, 1984-1986 (Box 36)
  - Journals: Hungary and Japan, 1987 (Box 36)
  - Journals: USA, 1970-1995 (Box 36, Box 37)
  - Journals: USSR, 1979 (Box 37)
  - Manual: Coalition on Government Information, 1985-1986 (Box 38)
  - Manual: Intellectual Freedom Committee, 1974 (Box 38)
  - Manual: Government Information Controls, 1988 (Box 38)
  - Scrapbook: Harrisburg Clips, 1970-1972 (Box 38)
- Personal Correspondence, 1934-2014
  Series is made up of letters and cards to Zoia Horn from friends and family from 1934 to 2014. Materials include letters from her husband Dean Galloway, her ex-husband Milton Horn, her brother Abe (Eric) Polisar, her daughters Pat and Catherine, and close friends Jean Allford, Sandy Berman, Fay Blake, Gene Chenoweth, Betty Wolfston, and Jerry Zietler.
  This series was set aside in a preliminary arrangement by Horn and has been kept in its original order.. Folders have been organized alphabetically by last name of correspondent.
  - Ackerman - Adler, 1967-2006 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Allford (Jean), 1968-2008 (Box 39, Folder 2-6, Box 40, Folder 1-3)
  - Bacon - Bagdikian, 1974-2008 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Baird - Barth, 1968-2014 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Blecher - Berman, 1979-2004 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Berrigan (Philip), 1997-2004 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Bidlack - Billowitz, 1966-1985 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Black (Allen), 1972-2007 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Blake - Blanchard, 1968-2006 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Bolinger - Boytinck, 1971-2001 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Brandon - Braverman, 1967-1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Brechman - Brooks, 1937-2002 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Bryant - Caldwell, 1962-2010 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Cards: Birthday, 1960-2012 (Box 41, Folder 7-8, Box 42, Folder 1-3)
  - Cards: Blank, 2000s (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
  - Cards: Get Well, 2000s (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Cards: Holiday, 1980-2012 (Box 43, Folder 1, Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Cards: Sympathy, 2000s (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Carney - Colbaugh, 1954-2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Cole - Cowupfell, 1966-2000 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Crawford - Crowley, 1984-2001 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Daniels - Drinnon, 1969-2008 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Elizabeth - Epstein, 1961-2003 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Erlich (Martin), 1999-2002 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Eshelman (Bill), 1967-1997 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Ewen - Eubanks, 1986-1992 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Fell (Pat), 1996-2010 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Fenton - Frederickson, 1935-2001 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Galloway (Dean), 1968-1976 (Box 47, Folder 1-4, Box 46, Box 45, Box 44, Folder 1-6)
  - Galloway (Susannah - Vivian), 1988-2008 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Gear (Sylva), 1968-1971 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Gilbert (Carol - Grace), 1965-2001 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Goldsmith - Goodman, 1994-1996 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Grass - Guilloux, 1931-1997 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Hankey - Heffron, 1940-2007 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Helligas-Heynmann, 1945-2001 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Hirsh - Horrocks, 1933-2008 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Horn (Milton), 1936-1965 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Hsien - Huish, 1930-2010 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Jackson (Clara), 1977-2003 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Jacob (Howard), 1965-1970 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Jenks - Jensen, 1989-2001 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Joe (Elaine), 2000-2014 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Johnson (Curtis), 1980-2006 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Jones (Carol), 1979-1992 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Keating - King, 1939-1992 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Kister - Kutler, 1938-2006 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Lausch - Little, 1993-2008 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - MacArthur-Manheimer, 1970-2010 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Marrion (Asia), 1997-2010 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Marrion (Catherine), 1967-2014 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Marsh - Mazza, 1966-1991 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Medsger (Betty), 1981-2009 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Menaker (Tom), 1987-1998 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Miller - Mollenkopf, 1955-2001 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Mobbs (Anne), 1993-2005 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Moon (Eric), 1956-2002 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Morris - Morrissett, 1965-1996 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Newman - O'Neill, 1934-2009 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Olver (Ruth), 1935-1937 (Box 50, Folder 8-9)
  - Patten (Isabelle), 1971-2003 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Peattie - Peters, 1984-1993 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Peterson (Jan), 1964-1990 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Plainfield - Pohl, 1956-1968 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Polisar (Abe), 1942-1995 (Box 51, Folder 4-7, Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - Polisar (Anne), 1954-2001 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Polisar (Dina), 1960-1989 (Box 52, Folder 4-6)
  - Polisar (John), 1967-2014 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Polisar (Lisa), 1966-2014 (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
  - Polisar (Kathy), 1966-2014 (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
  - Polisar (Mark), 1938-2008 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Postcards: Blank (Europe and North America), undated (Box 54)
  - Postcards: Blank (Asia and USSR), undated (Box 55)
  - Raymond - Rein, 1966-2008 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Rice (Eve), 2004-2006 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ricci (Phyllis), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Rinkus - Ruby, 1967-2004 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Russian Letters, 1997-1999 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Samoto (Sachiko), 1988-2003 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Saudel - Simmons, 1938-2003 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Shirley (H.G.), 1954-1967 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Slochower - Stanavage, 1939-1998 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Staff (Bobbie), 1937-1985 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
  - Tanier - Taruskin, 1966-2008 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Tate (Beth), 1942-2008 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Taylor (Ron), 1970-1972 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Tenenbaum (George), 1934-1938 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Thomas (Joan), 1960-1999 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
  - Thompson - Turek, 1966-2001 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Unsorted: First Name Only, 1950-2014 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
  - Vail - Volkersz, 1965-1989 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Waller - Weisberger, 1942-2006 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Weitzer (Lillian), 1943-1968 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Wershba (Joe), 1943-1991 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Wheatley - White, 1965-1989 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Wilson (Vivian), 1965-2005 (Box 59, Folder 4-5)
  - Withim (Gloria), 1974-2010 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Wolfston (Betsy), 2000s (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Worthen - Wrightson, 1997-2009 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Yoko, 2012-2013 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Young (Pat), 1938-1990 (Box 60, Folder 2-3)
  - Zeitlin (Jerry), 1937-1938 (Box 60, Folder 4-5)
- Biographical Information, 1943-2014
  Series is comprised of awards, certificates, organization and alumni newsletters, travel souvenirs, and personal health research, including prescriptions and doctors' notes, compiled by Zoia Horn. Materials include the California Library Hall of fame 2012 award, the 2002 Jackie Eubanks Memorial Award, teachers certificates and copies of college diplomas, and dozens of activist pins and lapel buttons. The series spans 1943 to 2014.
  This series was set aside in a preliminary arrangement by Horn and has been kept in its original order. Folders are sorted alphabetically by subject.
  - Awards Information, 1995-2012 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
  - General Information, 1965-2014 (Box 61, Folder 3-5)
  - Health Research, 1973-2006 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Activist Buttons, undated (Box 62)
  - Bookmarks, undated (Box 62)
  - California Library Hall of Fame Award, 2012 (Box 62)
  - Certificates, 1943-2004 (Box 62)
  - Jackie Eubanks Memorial Award, 2002 (Box 62)
- Books, 1940-2013
  This series contains the books in Zoia Horn's research library, spanning 1940 to 2013. Materials include books published by the American Library Association, volumes from the Right to Know journal, issues of The Progressive Librarian, the Japanese translation of Horn's memoir Zoia!, and address books.
  Items have been organized alphabetically by last name of the author or the name of the publishing organization.
  - Abdullahi (Ismail): E.J. Josey, an activist librarian, 1992 (Box 63)
  - American Library Association: Less Access to Less Information by and about the U.S. Government (1982-1987) (Box 63)
  - American Library Association: Less Access to Less Information by and about U.S. Government (1988-1991) (Box 63)
  - American Library Association: Loyalty Oaths, 1950-1992 (Box 63)
  - American Library Association: Policies, Foreign Nationals, 1974-1992 (Box 63)
  - American Library Association: Position Statements, Policies and Procedures, 1940-1992 (Box 63)
  - Bald (Margaret): Banned Books, Literature Suppressed on Religious Grounds, 1998 (Box 63)
  - Blake (Fay): Verbis Non Factis, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Brooklyn College: Alumni Directory, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Bucknell University: L'Agenda, 1971 (Box 63)
  - California Library Association: Intellectual Freedom Handbook, 1992 (Box 63)
  - Eshelman (William): A Gathering of Memories, 1921-2004 (Box 63)
  - Foerstel (Herbert): Surveillance in the Stacks, 1991 (Box 63)
  - Gage (April): Speaking Freely, 2006 (Box 63)
  - Horn (Zoia): Right to Know, Volumes 1-4, 1985-1992 (Box 63)
  - Horn (Zoia) and Samato (Sachiko): Zoia! (4 Copies), 1995 (Box 64)
  - Josey (E.J.): The Black Librarian in America Revisited, 1994 (Box 64)
  - Josey (E.J.): New Dimensions for Academic Library Service, 1975 (Box 64)
  - Journal of Information Ethics: Volumes 18-22, 2009-2013 (Box 64)
  - Karolides (Nicholas): Banned Books, Literature Suppressed on Political Grounds, 1998 (Box 64)
  - Karolides (Nicholas): 120 Banned Books, Censorship Histories of World Literature, 2005 (Box 64)
  - Katz (Bill): Library Lit. 6, The Best of 1975, 1976 (Box 64)
  - McFarland: Catalogue, 1995 (Box 64)
  - Moore (Everett): Issues of Freedom in American Libraries, 1964 (Box 64)
  - Peattie (Noel): A Passage for Dissent, 1989 (Box 64)
  - Progressive Librarian: Issues 32-35, 2009-2010 (Box 64)
  - Robbins (Louise): Censorship and the American Library, 1996 (Box 64)
  - Robbins (Louise): The Dismissal of Miss Ruth Brown, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Woodward (Diana): Library Trends, 1990 (Box 64)
  - Write-In Books: Address, Anniversary, Birthday, 2000s (Box 65)
- Photographs and Media, 1960-2014
  This series is comprised mainly of audio cassettes, video cassettes, DVDs, and photographs, spanning 1960 to 2014. Materials include interviews with Zoia Horn; family and work photos; and recordings from American Library Association conferences.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  SERIES CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  Items have been physically organized by item type, then alphabetically by subject. Due to size restrictions, similar items have been grouped together (audio cassettes with other audio cassettes, VHS tape with other VHS tapes, etc).
  - American Civil Liberties Union: Constitution and White House Secrecy and Accountability, undated (Box 66)
    One audio cassette. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - American Library Association: Censorship and the Right to Know, 1984 (Box 66)
  - American Library Association: Charging for Computer-Based Reference Service, 1977 (Box 66)
  - American Library Association: Cold War (1-2), undated (Box 66)
    Two audio cassettes. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - American Library Association: Conference, 1900s (Box 66)
  - American Library Association: IFC (1-3), 1977 (Box 66)
    Three audio cassettes. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - American Library Association: New York, 1974 (Box 66)
  - American Library Association: Treason and Government Secrecy, undated (Box 66)
  - Anna Epstein, 2003 (Box 66)
    One cassette. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Battle for the Pentagon Papers (1-2), 1991 (Box 66)
  - Body Recall, undated (Box 66)
  - Canada, Radio Noon, 1985 (Box 66)
  - Chomsky (Noam), 1996 (Box 66)
  - Civil Liberties Institute: Education Issues, 1981 (Box 66)
  - Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility: Future Libraries, 1996 (Box 66)
  - Culture and Values in America, 1994 (Box 66)
  - Dale Lotter, undated (Box 66)
  - Lines of Deceit: Cocaine and the White House, 1990 (Box 66)
  - Howard Zinn: Just and Unjust Wars, 1971 (Box 66)
  - Jim Hightower, undated (Box 66)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. at California Democratic Council, 1968 (Box 66)
  - Privatization Conference (1-2), undated (Box 66)
  - Unlabeled Audio Cassette, undated (Box 66)
  - What is Socialism? Paul Sweezey and Toby Cole, 1994 (Box 66)
  - Zoia Horn: Intellectual Freedom Institute 1975 (Box 66)
  - Zoia Horn and Esther Helfand, Ms. Magazine, 1980 October 26; yrlsc_2262_066_003; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:20:45) (Box 66, Case 3)
    CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    Scope and Contents
    Interview featuring Zoia and Esther speaking about censorship and intellectual freedom for "Between the Lines" radio program on K101FM
  - Amy Goodman in conversation with Orville Schell, 2005 (Box 67)
    One compact disc. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - April Gage with Zoia Horn, 2006 (Box 68)
  - Betsy Wolfston Art Work, undated (Box 68)
  - Zoia 39 Library Photos, undated (Box 68)
  - Zoia Oakland Library Photos, 2008 (Box 68)
  - Howard Zinn, You Can't Be Neutral, 2004 (Box 67)
    One DVD. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Interview with Dina Polisar, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Loose Change, undated (Box 67)
  - Memories, undated (Box 68)
  - War and Peace Trilogy, 2004 (Box 67)
  - Zoia Horn on Harrisburg Six at Buchnell University, 1971 February 20; yrlsc_2262_068_001; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:12:03) (Box 68, Case 1)
    Transcribed from container: "Comments by Zoia Horn Meeting on the Harrisburg Six, Vaughn Lit. Aud. Buchnell U. 2/20/71. Recorded by WVBU"
  - Photographs: American Library Association Conferences, San Francisco, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Art Print, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Avenue of Great Trees, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Brooklyn College 50th Anniversary Class, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: California, 1966-1967 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: California Forests, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Captain Starn's Restaurant, 1957-1958 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Cannon Beach, Oregon, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Data Center, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Los Angeles, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Main Bay Beach, undated (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Negatives, Strharsky and Templeton, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Personal and Professional Photos, 1960-2012 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: University of California, Los Angeles, 1965-1968 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Chotchke, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    One audio record. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Photographs: San Jose, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Asia Marrion's "Read Me A Story", 1999 (Box 68)
    One VHS tape. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Odessa to Kiev (1-2), 1989 (Box 67)
    Two VHS tapes. Audiovisual materials in this collection require the production of reference surrogates. To access audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - We the People, Coalition for the Right to Know, 1981 (Box 67)
  - Librarians vs. The Patriot Act, 2004 January 23; yrlsc_2262_068_002; Franklin, Craig; KRON-TV; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:06:18) (Box 68, Case 2)
    Transcribed from container: "Zoia Horn interviewed about Berrigan Trial and New Patriot Act" Zoia's interview begins at 0:02:12.
  - Zoia Horn's 75th Birthday, 1993 (Box 68)